{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "How can you get the type of arguments passed to a function?",
      "options": [
        "using typeof operator ",
        "using getType function",
        "Both of the above",
        "None of the above."
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following function of Number object returns a string value version of the current number?",
      "options": [
        "toString()",
        "toFixed()",
        " toLocaleString()",
        "toPrecision()"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Among the given statements, which statement defines closures in JavaScript?",
      "options": [
        "JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with references to its inner function scope",
        "JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with references to its lexical environment",
        " JavaScript is a function that is enclosed with the object to its inner function scope",
        "None of the mentioned"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Arrays in JavaScript are defined by which of the following statements?",
      "options": [
        "It is an ordered list of values",
        "It is an ordered list of objects",
        "It is an ordered list of string",
        "It is an ordered list of functions"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is Client-side JavaScript code is embedded within HTML documents?",
      "options": [
        "A URL that uses the special javascript:code",
        "A URL that uses the special javascript:protocol",
        "A URL that uses the special javascript:encoding",
        "A URL that uses the special javascript:stack"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following object is the main entry point to all client-side JavaScript features and APIs?",
      "options": ["Position", "Window", "Standard", "Location"],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following can be used to call a JavaScript Code Snippet?",
      "options": ["Function/Method", "Preprocessor", "Triggering Event", "RMI"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": " Which of the following explains correctly what happens when a JavaScript program is developed on a Unix Machine?",
      "options": [
        "will work perfectly well on a Windows Machine",
        "will be displayed as JavaScript text on the browser",
        "will throw errors and exceptions",
        "must be restricted to a Unix Machine only"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Why event handlers is needed in JS?",
      "options": [
        " Allows JavaScript code to alter the behaviour of windows",
        "Adds innerHTML page to the code",
        "Change the server location",
        "Performs handling of exceptions and occurrences"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 20
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is true about cookie handling in JavaScript?",
      "options": [
        "JavaScript can manipulate cookies using the cookie property of the Document object.",
        "JavaScript can read, create, modify, and delete the cookie or cookies that apply to the current web page.",
        "Both of the above.",
        "None of the above."
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the correct JavaScript statement to print the addition of two numbers 10 and 20 in a paragraph whose id is 'result'?",
      "options": [
        "getElementById('result').innerHTML = 10+20;",
        "getElementById('result').innerHTML = '10+20';",
        "getElementById('#result').innerHTML = 10+20;",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "The const keyword is used to define a ______.",
      "options": [
        "Function scopes variable",
        "Block scoped variable",
        "Constant",
        "Constant with no initial value"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the main difference between var and let keywords in JavaScript?",
      "options": [
        "var defines a variable while let defines a constant",
        "var defined function scoped variable while let define block scoped variable",
        "The value of a variable declared with var can be changed while the value of a variable declared with let cannot be changed",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "correctOption": 1,
      "points": 30
    },
    {
      "question": "Which JavaScript method is used to call a function (a callback function) once for each array element?",
      "options": ["for()", "traverse()", "forEach()", "foreach()"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which JavaScript method is used to create a new array with array elements that passes a test?",
      "options": ["forEach()", "map()", "forMap()", "filter()"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 20
    }
  ]
}
